SUPER HOSTILE 

RACE FOR WOOL #02: Direct Fire
Version 1.1

by Vechs

=========================

Hey gang, Vechs here, and thank you for downloading Super Hostile : Race for Wool 02.

This is a Super Hostile map specifically for multiplayer, with support for up to 18 players on two teams (9 on each team), although it was designed for primarily for 2 to 4 players on a team.

HOW TO PLAY:

The map is divided into two identical lanes.  Each team plays on a lane, and rushes to place colored wool blocks on their Victory Monument, the first team to place all the blocks wins.

Each lane is 16 blocks wide, and once the map has started (Both teams leave the starting platform.)  players are STRICTLY FORBIDDEN from leaving their lanes.  At no point may players leave the 16 block width of their lane, and if they do, the other team may, at their descretion, claim victory and disqualify the offending team.  Should an explosion or other game effect move a player off their lane involuntarily, the player must immediatly fall into the void and die (likely to happen anyway, but the player might land on a block between lanes...).

However, players may, upon both teams consensus prior to the map starting, act upon each other with ranged techniques -- as long as the players stay within their area, they may shoot arrows, push blocks via pistons, and use TNT cannons, or other available techniques to harass and slow down the other team. 

(It is in the spirit of the map for players to be as hostile and confrontational to the other team as possible.  In other words, they should be SUPER HOSTILE to each other.)

>:D

Should a player die and not have a bed available to respawn at, they must leave the starting platform and immediatly return to their lane.

Players make break blocks, craft, and for the most part play Minecraft as normal, but they must aquire the goal wools from chests in the map, and not use dyes to aquire the wool colors.  Players are also prohibited from moving on top of the map ceiling, should such a roof be present.

For shorter games, players may agree to play for specific wools -- for example, a game until Green Wool is aquired, or a game until Green and Blue are aquired.

====================================

Recommended Rule:

Players should agree to not target the enemy Victory Monument with TNT canons.  However, the rules of engagement are up to the player to decide before the game starts, and making defenses for your monument while at the same time trying to shoot the enemies might make for some fun and hectic gameplay.

